Contact

9560297049 (Mobile) rajshoji@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rajnishprajapat-4bb12183 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Start-ups
Entrepreneurship
Marketing

Languages

English (Professional Working) Hindi (Full Professional)

Rajnish Prajapat

Building FinTech Product | Growth Hacker | Founded Two Startups In College

Gurgaon

Summary

I Skipped the useless education of college and Founded two startups while in college.

I have also served as a President of the Student union and worked with the Govt of India to establish Startup Center of Innovation and Entrepreneurship across 7 States.

Now I have been working on a Travel Tech Startup and helping startup Founders to grow their companies faster.

I have helped more than 10 startups to acquire combined of 3 Million Users and Expected Revenue of more than \$10 Million in Media, Fintech, Edutech, Saas and Travel Tech Industry.

If you need help in growth of your startup, I would be happy to help you.

Have something interesting to discuss? Shoot a mail at Rajnish@pocktrip.com

Experience

Gurgaon, India

Wealthian Co-founder & Head of Growth October 2019 - Present (11 months)

I am responsible to take care of revenue growth and Marketing. In 9 months, Wealthian grew from Zero revenue to \$120k per month.

Kundan Kishore Contributor May 2020 - Present (4 months) Gurgaon, Haryana, India Startups
Product & Growth consultant
August 2018 - Present (2 years 1 month)
Gurgaon, India

I help startups to grow faster and achieve competitive advantage within limited budget. So far I have helped more than 10 startups to generate \$10 Million in revenue.

Eco Mitra Investor & Mentor January 2020 - Present (8 months) Jaipur, Rajasthan

Eco mitra is into manufacturing and B2B trading of bio degradable products. Company has been processing more than 40 products into the market with large supply chain management.

Josh Talks Growth Consultant December 2019 - January 2020 (2 months) Gurgaon, India

Josh Talks is a Media company with the mission to inspire, empower and skill future generations of the world. Josh Talks have touched the lives of more than 300 Million through online distribution of content and reached every corner (well, almost) of Digital Bharat.

- Leading cross-functional campaigns for a product launch or demand generation and specify messaging and offers as well as desired outcomes like responses, MQL and ROI.
- Improving existing, and identify new, acquisition channels including AR (Analyst Relations), Facebook Marketing, paid search engine marketing (SEM), search engine optimization (SEO), account-based marketing (ABM), and affiliate marketing.
- Handling the growth for Josh Talks, including brand, customer acquisition, user engagement and the resulting financial performance.

PockTrip
Founder
September 2019 - January 2020 (5 months)

Gurgaon, India

India has 625 middle-class people who does not travel because budget does not fit into their pocket. That's why we (a few travellers and entrepreneurs) building PockTrip to help everyone travel debt free.

Project Eco Earth Investor September 2018 - June 2019 (10 months) New Delhi Area, India

Project Eco Earth is a social enterprise which recycles waste plastic materials and develops beautiful products by setting up Micro factories. The Aim of the Project is to create millions of micro-entrepreneurs and reducing plastic pollution in the world.

Indira Gandhi National Open University Startup mentor February 2019 - March 2019 (2 months)

National Institute of Technology Delhi President (Student Union) September 2017 - July 2018 (11 months) New Delhi Area, India

Startup center for Innovation and entrepreneurship(SCIE)
Advisory Board Member
November 2016 - May 2018 (1 year 7 months)
New Delhi Area, India

Start-up Centre for Innovation and Entrepreneurship (SCIE), is a centre established by Govt of India. This is an initiative by the central government. While the Union ministry of human resource development will provide 25 lakh per year, the Directorate of science and technology will offer an equal amount as the aid for the centre.

Surexpert
Founder and CEO
August 2016 - April 2017 (9 months)
New Delhi Area, India

It was an online service for entrepreneurs to give and get relevant advice over the phone. We made it easy for you to find, schedule and pay for expert advice over the phone to grow your business.

• In March 2017, the company was able to facilitate to around 200 mentors of different domains and 37,200 users.

Oopadai Founder and CEO October 2015 - September 2016 (1 year)

New Delhi Area, India

Oopadai was a web-based platform that helps prospective college applicants get authentic, relevant and current advice about campus life, courses, finances directly from high achieving, current college students already attending their target universities.

• In July 2016, Oopadai's user base reached at around 80,000 users with adding 1200 users daily.

Safeshop India Product Marketing Manager August 2014 - December 2015 (1 year 5 months) New Delhi

I was responsible for sale of reliance, Grasim suit lengths, Fashion-line of United Colours of Benetton and Reebok, Lavanya Lavanya sarees, Samsung, Nokia and Philips. I built a high-performing team of 100 members by the end of the first year and sold more than 10 million rupees in products.

Education

National Institute of Technology Delhi B.tech, Electrical and Electronics Engineering